(PIANO MUSIC)
♪ OH ♪
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
♪ OH, OH ♪
♪ SWEET LOVE, YEAH ♪
♪ I DIDN'T MEAN IT WHEN I
SAID I DIDN'T LOVE YOU SO ♪
♪ I SHOULDA HELD ON TIGHT,
I NEVER SHOULDA LET YOU GO ♪
♪ I DIDN'T KNOW NOTHING, I
WAS STUPID, I WAS FOOLISH ♪
♪ I WAS LYING TO MYSELF ♪
♪ I COULDN'T HAVE
FATHOMED I WOULD EVER
BE WITHOUT YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ NEVER IMAGINED I'D BE
SITTING HERE BESIDE MYSELF ♪
♪ GUESS I DIDN'T KNOW YOU,
GUESS I DIDN'T KNOW ME ♪
♪ BUT I THOUGHT I KNEW
EVERYTHING I NEVER FELT ♪
♪ THE FEELING THAT
I'M FEELING NOW ♪
♪ THAT I DON'T HEAR YOUR VOICE ♪
♪ OR HAVE YOUR TOUCH
AND KISS YOUR LIPS ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE ♪
♪ OH, WHAT I WOULDN'T GIVE TO
HAVE YOU LYING BY MY SIDE ♪
♪ RIGHT HERE, 'CAUSE,
BABY, WE BELONG TOGETHER ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LEFT, I
LOST A PART OF ME ♪
♪ IT'S STILL SO
HARD TO BELIEVE ♪
♪ COME BACK, BABY, PLEASE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE BELONG TOGETHER ♪
♪ WHO ELSE AM I GONNA LEAN
ON WHEN TIMES GET ROUGH ♪
♪ WHO'S GONNA TALK TO ME ON THE
PHONE 'TIL THE SUN COMES UP ♪
♪ WHO'S GONNA TAKE YOUR PLACE,
THERE AIN'T NOBODY BETTER ♪
♪ OH, BABY, BABY,
WE BELONG TOGETHER ♪
♪ I CAN'T SLEEP AT NIGHT,
WHEN YOU ARE ON MY MIND ♪
♪ BOBBY WOMACK'S ON THE RADIO ♪
♪ SINGING TO ME, IF YOU
THINK YOU'RE LONELY NOW ♪
♪ WAIT A MINUTE, THIS
IS TOO DEEP, TOO DEEP ♪
♪ I GOTTA CHANGE THE STATION ♪
♪ SO I TURN THE DIAL,
TRYING TO CATCH A BREAK ♪
♪ AND THEN I HEAR BABYFACE,
I ONLY THINK OF YOU ♪
♪ AND IT'S BREAKING MY HEART ♪
♪ I'M TRYNA KEEP IT TOGETHER,
BUT I'M FALLING APART ♪
♪ I'M FEELING ALL
OUT OF MY ELEMENT ♪
♪ THROWING THINGS, CRYING ♪
♪ TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHERE
THE HELL I WENT WRONG ♪
♪ THE PAIN REFLECTED
IN THIS SONG ♪
♪ AIN'T EVEN HALF OF
WHAT I'M FEELING INSIDE ♪
♪ I NEED YOU, NEED YOU
BACK IN MY LIFE, BABY ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LEFT, I
LOST A PART OF ME ♪
♪ IT'S STILL SO
HARD TO BELIEVE ♪
♪ COME BACK, BABY, PLEASE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE BELONG TOGETHER ♪
♪ WHO ELSE AM I GONNA LEAN
ON WHEN TIMES GET ROUGH ♪
♪ WHO'S GONNA TALK TO ME ON THE
PHONE 'TIL THE SUN COMES UP ♪
♪ WHO'S GONNA TAKE YOUR PLACE,
THERE AIN'T NOBODY BETTER ♪
♪ OH, BABY, BABY, WE
BELONG TOGETHER, BABY ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LEFT, I
LOST A PART OF ME ♪
♪ IT'S STILL SO
HARD TO BELIEVE ♪
♪ COME BACK, BABY, PLEASE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE BELONG TOGETHER ♪
♪ WHO AM I GONNA LEAN ON
WHEN TIMES GET ROUGH ♪
♪ WHO'S GONNA TALK TO ME
'TIL THE SUN COMES UP ♪
♪ WHO'S GONNA TAKE YOUR PLACE,
THERE AIN'T NOBODY BETTER ♪
♪ OH, BABY, BABY,
WE BELONG TOGETHER ♪
♪ WHO WILL, WHO WILL, WHO WILL
AHH ♪
♪♪♪